This is a work of fiction.
Underage drinking is strongly prohibited and illegal.
Scenes involving alcohol with forceful consumption
and shameful acts are not encouraged.
Please view this as a comedy.
Furthermore, all characters appearing
in this work are of legal age.
♪～
Be passionate, my friends
Shine bright with the sun
Dive into the blue sky
And let summer take it all
Grand Blue Dreaming
Be passionate, my friends
Shine bright with the sun
Dive into the blue sky
And let summer take it all
An expanding ocean of possibilities
Summer is our amore
We'll swear to the crystal clear sky
Summer is in our hands
Be passionate, my friends
Shine bright with the sun
Dive into the blue sky
And let summer take it all
With a cheerful heart
Don't mess with me
Keep going even if you fall
And let summer take it all
～♪
（盛り上がる声）
This work is an original copyrighted material
of the Content Provider. Unauthorized reproduction
or distribution of this work in any form or manner
is prohibited. Some viewers might find this work disturbing
as it may contain strong language, a degree of violence
or adult situations. Viewer discretion is advised.
Please watch it at your own risk.
The story, names, characters and incidents portrayed
in this work are fictitious. No identification with actual
persons, organizations, religions, places and products
is intended. The Content Provider, the producers
and related parties shall have no liability,
as to the accuracy, legality, safety or suitability
for any purpose of the information provided in this work.
The views and opinions expressed herein do not reflect
the views and opinions of the Content Provider,
or any of its affiliates, partners, subsidiaries, or Licensee.
（伊織(いおり)）いやあ あの子 怒ってたな
（耕平(こうへい)）だな
-Yeah. That girl was mad.
-Yeah.
Whose fault is that?
（御手洗(みたらい)）誰のせいだ 誰の！
Yours.
（一同）お前だが？
Don't you feel guilty at all?
（御手洗）なぜ みじんも
罪の意識がないんだ？
お前らに 友の幸せを願う
優しさはないのか！
Can't you be nice? Can't you be happy for your friend?
その言葉 そっくりそのまま
返してやる
I'd like to say the same thing to you.
（野島(のじま)）別に 俺だって―
I didn't say you can't get a girlfriend.
“彼女を作るな”と
言ってるわけじゃない
ほう？
（野島）ただ―
But, if you're going to get a girlfriend, be prepared to die.
That's all.
“彼女を作るなら死を覚悟しろ”
と言ってるだけなんだ
（山本(やまもと)）ヘッ いいこと言うぜ
Well put.
We're best friends, right?
（藤原(ふじわら)）俺たち 親友だもんな
These guys are crazy.
こいつら 頭 ヤベえぞ
（耕平）類友だろ
Birds of a feather, right?
Then...
じゃあ…
（野島たち）ん？
Then when are we ever going to get girlfriends?
じゃあ 俺たちは
いつ彼女ができるんだ！
（一同）うっ！
（山本）言われてみれば…
You're right.
We spent too much time in your way.
抜け駆けの妨害に
傾倒するあまり…
No. It's fine.
いや 大丈夫だ
It's fine?
（山本）大丈夫だと？
This is what an idiot once said:
前に とあるバカが
こう言っていた
If one of us makes friends with them,
we can set up another mixer!
（伊織）誰かが仲よくなれば
また合コンが組める
You'll do it for us, right?
You're the guy with the girlfriend.
（野島）なあ
やってくれるよなあ？　彼女持ち
Wait! Wait! Wait!
I already set up that mixer, right?
待て待て待て！
合コンは前にも組んだだろ！
I can't keep doing that!
そんなに何度も組めるか！
We'll pay 5000 yen per person.
（野島）１人 5,000円出す
I'd be happy to help out a friend!
友の幸せのため
一肌 脱がせてくれ
So how can we get Chisa to accept?
んで どうやったら
千紗(ちさ)が了承すると思う？
知るか 俺には関係ない
Who knows? I'm not involved.
分け前 やるから
You'll get your share!
We could get her to play a penalty game.
罰ゲームに
かこつけたらどうだ
ああ なるほどな
となると 王様ゲームあたりか…
I see.
I guess we should do Truth or Dare.
Something like that.
（耕平）そのへんだろ
問題は―
The only problem will be getting Kotegawa to play.
いかに古手川(こてがわ)を王様ゲームに
引きずり込むかだが
Well, I'll figure it out.
まあ そのへんはうまくやるさ
Yeah.
（話し声）
That should do it.
（愛菜(あいな)）へえ そうなんだ
Hey, you two.
（伊織）２人とも
（愛菜･千紗）ん？
Would you like some?
（伊織）これ どうだ？
お刺身？
（千紗）伊織がさばいたの？
-Sashimi?
-Are you the one who cut it?
Yeah. Can you taste it for me?
ああ 味見してもらえるか？
Okay.
うん…
You know how to cut fish?
伊織って
魚 さばけるんだ…
（愛菜･千紗）あ…
（伊織）王様ゲーム！
Truth or dare!
（一同）イエ～！
Yeah!
（愛菜･千紗）え？
えっ… そんな…
Hold on!
Everyone has to draw one!
（伊織）さあ 全員 引いて！
One, two...
せーの！
（一同）王様だーれだ！
（愛菜）はい ストーップ！
Who's the king?
All right! Stop!
どうした ケバ子
（耕平）なぜ止める ケバ子
-What's wrong, Cakey?
-Why are you stopping us?
Don't call me Cakey!
ケバ子 言うな！
Knock it off, Aina.
（梓(あずさ)）ダメだよ 愛菜
If you draw, you have to play.
（時田(ときた)）くじを引いたら
参加しないとな
He gave me this for the sashimi.
これは 刺身に使えって
渡されただけで…
What do you mean?
何を言うか
Try remembering what Kitahara said just now.
さっき 北原(きたはら)が言ったことを
思い出せ
Would you like some?
これ どうだ？
The word "sashimi" was never said, right?
（耕平･伊織）刺身とは
一度も言ってないよなあ？
（愛菜）卑劣！
That was dirty!
（奈々華(ななか)）
まあ そうイヤがらないで ね？
Don't be so mad, okay?
Just try it once. You can quit if you don't like it.
一度やってみて イヤだったら
やめてもいいからさ
What do you want to do?
どうする？
ハァ… 一度だけなら
Just once.
Great! Let's try this again!
（伊織）よっしゃ！
じゃあ 改めて…
Who's the king?
（一同）王様だーれだ！
（千紗･愛菜）うう…
（梓）ウッフフ… 私だね
It's me.
-Give us your orders.
-Okay.
（耕平）では 命令を
（梓）オッケー
Everyone except for me...
んじゃ “私以外の全員は―”
has to keep playing until the end!
“このゲームに
最後までつきあうこと”
-She got us.
（愛菜･千紗）やられた…
Why do you want us to play so badly?
どうして そこまで
参加させたがるんですか！
I wonder why...
どうしてだろうねえ…
You have to obey the king's orders, Chisa-chan.
王様の命令は
絶対なんですって 千紗ちゃん
You want us to play, too?
（千紗）お姉ちゃんまで…
（伊織）バカめ その２人は
すでに買収済みよ！
You idiots! We've already bought those two out!
A FEW HOURS EARLIER
-Truth or dare?
-I see.
王様ゲームかあ…
（奈々華）そうねえ…
（伊織）どうでしょうか？
What do you think?
うん オッケー
（奈々華）私も
-Okay!
-I'm okay with it, too.
マジですか!?
Really?
（梓）アハハハ 変なの
-You're so weird!
-Why are you so surprised?
（奈々華）どうして驚いてるの？
Well, I just thought you'd say no.
いや てっきり
断られるものとばかり…
PLAY TRICKS ON CHISA
PLAY TRICKS ON NANAKA
Well... Nothing bad will happen, right?
（伊織）まあ ひどいことには
ならないよな
（奈々華･梓）エヘヘヘ…
（千紗）ううっ…
（愛菜）ん？
Round two! Here we go!
（寿(ことぶき)）じゃあ ２回戦いくぞ～！
（一同）王様だーれだ！
Who's the king?
Oh, it's me again.
ありゃ また私だ
（伊織）連続ですか
Two in a row?
引きが強いな
You're good.
じゃあ 命令はね…
Well, then... I order numbers 1 through 7
to take something off.
“１から７番の人は１枚脱ぐ”で
（奈々華）あ…
（時田たち）むんっ！
（愛菜）脱ぐの早すぎるんですけど
You guys strip too fast!
Come on, take it off, Nanaka!
さあさあ
奈々華も脱いで脱いで
えーっと… それじゃ…
Okay...
（耕平･伊織）フオ～！
（愛菜）ストーップ！
Stop!
What's wrong, Aina?
どうしたの？　愛菜ちゃん
Taking off a sock is enough, right?
脱ぐにしても 靴下で十分ですから
（伊織･耕平）チッ！
I'll let you off this time.
今回は 見逃すけど
I see.
そっかそっか
No more dirty orders like that!
今後 そういう
いやらしい命令はＮＧです！
（梓）えーっ
（耕平･伊織）えーっ
Who's the king?
（一同）王様だーれだ！
It's me!
（愛菜）私です
（耕平･伊織）うう…
What's your order?
（時田）命令はなんだ
Nothing too crazy, okay?
一応 常識の範ちゅうでな
分かりました　じゃあ―
Okay!
-Numbers 1 through 7...
-Yeah?
“１から７番の全員は…”
（時田･寿）おう！
can't strip at the next party!
“次の飲み会で
服を脱がないこと”
（寿･時田）ああ…
We have to obey...
王様の命令は…
（寿）絶対…
The king's orders.
An order about wearing clothes? That's too crazy!
服の着脱に関する命令は
常識外れだろ！
You should be ashamed!
（耕平）恥を知れ 恥を！
Telling you to keep your clothes on isn't crazy!
（愛菜）常識のために
脱ぐなって言ってんの！
It can't be helped.
（寿）まあ しかたない
We'll do our best to deal with it.
前向きに善処する方向で
検討しよう
Promise me, okay?
（愛菜）約束ですからね
じゃ 次いくよ！
Let's play the next round.
（一同）王様だーれだ！
Who's the king?
It's me this time!
今度は私ね
じゃあね“３番の人が…”
Well, then... Number 3...
I'm safe!
（伊織）よし セーフ！
Has to tell the person to the left
that she loves her sister!
“左隣の人に―”
“お姉ちゃん大好きって
愛の告白をしてください”
（伊織）なるほど…
I get it...
Hey. Don't be embarrassed. Say it.
ほら てれずに告白してこい
（千紗）え？
You're number 3, right?
３番って お前なんだろ？
No, I'm not.
いや 違うけど
（伊織）え？
うっ！　待て じゃあ 誰が…
Wait! Then who is--?
（寿）私です…
It's me.
This is wrong!
これはダメです！
絶対 トラウマになるやつです！
This is going to be traumatic!
これはダメです！
絶対 トラウマになるやつです！
（寿）お姉ちゃん
お姉ちゃん…
（奈々華）えーっと…
（千紗）伊織 うるさい
-Sister...
-Shut up, Iori.
You have to obey the king's orders, right?
（愛菜）王様の命令は
絶対なんでしょ？
お姉ちゃん…
I love you, sister!
（寿）お姉ちゃん 大好き！
（伊織）イヤー！
Who's the king?
（一同）王様だーれだ！
Bad dreams...
夢に見る… 絶対夢に見る…
I'm going to have bad dreams about this.
フン 俺です！
（伊織）ハッ！
It's me!
I got it, Kitahara!
（耕平）引いたぞ 北原！
（伊織）でかした 耕平！
You did it, Kohei!
All we have to do is find out what number Chisa drew.
（伊織）あとは 千紗が
何番を引いたかだが…
あの割り箸には
細工がしてある
We rigged these chopsticks.
The ones with unequal lengths are odd,
and the regular ones are even.
先端の長さが
違うものが奇数で
同じものが偶数
The ones with round tips are in the first half,
and the square ones are the second half!
先端が丸みを帯びて
いるのが―
前半の数字で
四角いのが
後半の数字
（奈々華）どう？
（千紗）うーん
Well...
From the looks of those chopsticks,
Chisa is number 1 or number 3!
（伊織）あの形状だと
千紗は１番か３番！
Only two possibilities!
You can do it, Kohei!
あとは２択だ
任せたぞ 耕平！
Okay!
（耕平）ＯＫ！
Kohei, give us your orders.
（奈々華）じゃあ 耕平君
命令をどうぞ
Okay! I order you to introduce your friends
to the king at our next party!
はい 俺の命令は―
“今度 王様に飲み会で
友達を紹介する”です
（愛菜･千紗）え？
（梓）何番の人が？
-Which number?
-Well, that's...
それは無論…
（伊織）フッ…
Number 4!
（耕平）４番です！
（伊織）ガッ…
（伊織）なんで４番だよ
このバカ！
Why did you pick 4, you idiot?
You held up four fingers!
お前が４本指を
立てたんだろうが！
I tried to say Chisa is number 1 or 3, idiot!
あれは 千紗が
１番か３番だって…
Those guys really were up to something.
やっぱり また
なんかたくらんでた
（千紗）ハァ…
Okay, okay. That's enough fighting.
はいはい ケンカはそこまでね
（伊織）ハァ… やれやれ
（耕平）作戦失敗か…
-Oh, dear.
-Our plan failed.
Don't be a sore loser.
So, what were you trying to do?
で 何が目的だったの？
目的っていうと
Our objective? Well...
It's a long story.
話せば長くなるんだが
Make it short.
（千紗）端的にまとめて
Money and women.
（伊織･耕平）金と女
You guys are terrible.
（愛菜･千紗）最低
You're mistaken.
それは誤解だ
Some guys promised us money
if we set up a mixer.
俺たちは 合コンを組んだら
金を受け取る約束で
This is a club activity to raise money for our trip.
これは いわば 合宿費用のための
サークル活動なんだ
Oh, really?
はいはい そうですか
Why don't you try working again?
また バイトでもして稼いだら？
It's hopeless.
とりつく島もねえ…
Too bad. Let's think of another way to get money.
しかたない
別の金策を考えるか
There's no time. We have to hurry.
時間もないから急がないとな
Choose something respectable this time.
（愛菜）今度は
真面目な方法にしなさいよ
Yeah.
（伊織･耕平）へーい
（奈々華）あっ ２人とも待って
（耕平･伊織）はい？
-Wait, you two.
-What?
一応 さっきの命令も
実行しないとね
We have to carry out the order just now.
（伊織･耕平）は？
（時田）はああ…
MEAT IZAKAYA
BULGING MUSCLES
Hey! So you're the guys Tokita was talking about!
（ラグビー部員）おう！
お前らが 時田が言ってた後輩か！
You want to have a crazy party, right?
（ラグビー部員）よっぽど
激しい飲み会がしたいんだな！
Do you want to join our club?
（空手部員）
ついでに うちの部員になるか？
What's going on?
（野島）どうなってんだ コラ！
（山本）こんなんで
金 もらえると思うなよ！
We're not going to pay you for this!
You should be paying us for this!
（御手洗）むしろ
お前らが払え ボケ！
うるせえ！　こっちも
やるだけやったんだ！
Shut up! We did our best!
You should pay us in recognition of our effort!
努力をねぎらって
金をよこせ！
No way!
（野島たち）
知るかー！
So do you have enough for the trip now?
結局 合宿のお金は
なんとかなったの？
まだ 足りなくてな…
Not yet.
I'm going to work tomorrow.
明日 稼いでくるんだ
It's a respectable job, right?
まともなバイトでしょうね
We're going to be event staff. Azusa introduced us.
梓さんの紹介で
イベントスタッフをな
（笛の音）
うわ キツそう…
Whoa, sounds hard.
短期バイトが
それしかなかったんだ
That's the only short-term job there was.
-If you need money, how about coming?
-They're okay with you just showing up.
（伊織）金が足りなかったら
一緒にどうだ？
（耕平）飛び込みＯＫらしいぞ
-I'm going to decline.
-Me too.
遠慮しとく
（千紗）私も
Hi!
（伊織）こんちゃーす
-Hey.
-All four of you came together?
（時田）おう
（寿）４人一緒か
近くで偶然 会いまして
We ran into each other nearby.
（梓）ダイコンが安いんだよねえ
（奈々華）いいわねえ
Radishes are so cheap.
Nice.
You need radishes?
大根がいるんですか？
I was wondering what to do.
どうしようかと思ってね
もう１本 欲しいんだけど
予算オーバーで
We wanted one more.
But it's over our budget.
じゃあ 俺が買ってきますよ
Then I'll go buy one.
Well, that's...
Don't worry about it.
そんな遠慮しなくても
Well, you know...
（梓）いやあ だって ねえ？
（奈々華）そうねえ
You're right.
They're pretty expensive.
（奈々華･梓）結構 高い物だし
How broke do they think I am?
（伊織）俺 どんだけ
金がないと思われてるんだろう
いやいや いくら俺でも
大根１本くらい買えますって
No...
It's just one radish! I can afford it!
（奈々華･梓）ん？　ああ…
Iori...
あのね 伊織君…
ねえ ちーちゃん 伊織が
ダイコン買ってくれたらどうする？
Hey, Chii-chan.
What are you going to do if Iori buys a radish?
（伊織）ん？
Fifteen minutes...
じゅ… 15分だけ…
I'll treat you like a human for fifteen minutes.
15分だけ 人間扱い
してあげてもいいです
だってさ 伊織
Hear that, Iori?
I wonder what she's been treating me like until now.
むしろ 今まで何扱いされてたのか
気になるところです
でも 大根が欲しいなんて
どうしたんです？
But why do you want a radish?
アハハハ
（奈々華）違うよ 伊織君
That's not it, Iori.
We were talking about di-com, not daikon.
大根じゃなくて
ダイコンの話をしてたの
-Di-com?
-Yeah.
（伊織）ダイコン？
（梓）そう
Dive computers.
ダイブコンピューター
のこと
They cost about this much.
ちなみに値段は これくらい
You were going to make me buy this?
お前 これだけの物を
買わせておいて…
I compromised as much as I could.
（千紗）最大限
譲歩したつもりだけど
んじゃ 全員そろったし 行くか
Now that we're all here, let's go.
Yeah.
（梓）そうだね
（伊織）え？　どこへです？
Where are we going?
We're going to look at diving gear today.
（時田）今日は
ダイビングの器材を見ようと思う
（耕平･愛菜･伊織）おお～！
There's lots of different gear.
ずいぶん いろいろな機材が
あるんだなあ
I don't know what to look for.
正直 何を見て回れば
いいのか分からん
Is there something we should buy?
何か 買っておくべき物は
あるんだろうか
They said rentals were okay in the beginning.
最初はレンタルで十分って
言われたが
That's what they told me too.
うん 私もそう言われた
I guess you need a towel and a swimsuit.
とりあえず タオル類と水着かしら
A swimsuit?
み… 水着ですか？
-Yeah!
-That's right!
（寿）おう
（時田）そのとおりだ
（時田･寿）
最初はタオルだけあればいい
-All you need is a towel for now!
-I see.
（耕平･伊織）なるほど
（愛菜）え？　水着は？
What about a swimsuit?
When you buy your own gear,
you should start with a mask.
（時田）自分の機材を買うなら
最初はマスクがオススメだ
Why?
（伊織）どうしてです？
They're pretty cheap.
（寿）まあ 比較的購入しやすい
値段というのもあるが
The main purpose of diving
is to see what it looks like underwater.
何より ダイビングの目的は
海の中を見ることだからな
You don't want a mask that makes it hard to see.
自分に合わないマスクで
見づらかったらイヤだろう？
（伊織･耕平）確かに
You're right.
Some people say you should buy a dive computer first.
ほかには ダイコンから
そろえるべきという考え方もある
They say you should get your own safety gear
to prevent decompression sickness.
自分用の安全機材を持って―
減圧症などのリスクを
減らそうという考えだな
We've never worn dive computers before.
俺たち 今までダイコンなんて
つけてないんですが…
Was that okay?
大丈夫だったんですか？
それは心配無用だ
Don't worry.
危険な深さまで
潜らせていないからな
You didn't dive to a dangerous depth.
（時田）それに そういったことが
起きないように―
The instructors are careful not to let that happen.
インストラクターが
目を光らせている
Divers who dive deep or swim far away
from their instructor need this gear.
（寿）ある程度の深さに
潜ったり―
インストラクターから離れて
動き回るダイバーに―
必要な機材ってわけだ
あ… これはなんですか？
What's this?
カレントフックだ
文字どおり 引っかけて使う
It's a reef hook.
You use it by hooking it.
-What's this?
-It's a float.
（耕平）これは？
（時田）フロートだ
You put air in it and blow it up.
中にエアを入れて 膨らませて使う
（伊織･耕平）なるほど
I see.
（耕平）んがっ！
（伊織）今 助ける！
I'll save you!
（耕平）北原ー！
It's scary underwater.
海の中って怖いな…
Yeah.
まったくだ フフッ…
（愛菜）あの顔 絶対
バカなこと考えてる…
That face... he's probably
thinking about something stupid.
じゃ 自由に見て回っていいぞ
Have a look around.
If you have any questions, just ask us.
分からないことがあったら
声をかけてくれ
-Okay.
-Okay!
（伊織･耕平）うーっす
（愛菜）はーい
はあ…
What are you looking at?
何を見てるんです？
ちょっと珍しいカメラだよ
It's an unusual camera.
You can take pictures like this.
（千紗）こういう形で
撮影できるんだって
確かに これは珍しいな
That is pretty unusual!
It's interesting, right?
おもしろいよねえ
ハッ！　伊織 伊織
（伊織）ん？
Iori. Iori!
-Hurry!
-What?
（千紗）早く
（伊織）なんだ なんだ
-They also have these.
-What's that?
（千紗）ほかには こんなのも
（伊織）これは？
It's a device for talking underwater.
水中で会話ができる機械みたいよ
（伊織）マジですか!?
Seriously?
（千紗）
骨伝導で音を拾うんだって
It picks up sound through your bones.
Modern science is amazing!
現代科学ってすげえ…
（千紗）ただ 会話には
少しだけコツがいるみたい
There's a trick to talking through this.
（伊織）本当だ
You're right. It's good to agree on the words in advance.
“事前に 使う単語を
打ち合わせておくとグッド”か
It's hard to talk when you have a regulator on.
（梓）レギュをくわえてると
発音しにくいもんね
Excuse me! I have a question.
（愛菜）
すみません ちょっと質問が…
（千紗）あ…
（梓）どうしたの？
What's wrong?
レギュレーターは
どうやって選べばいいですか？
How do you choose a regulator?
（梓）え？　レギュ？
A regulator?
You'll be fine with a rental.
（千紗）まだ レンタルで
いいと思うけど
（愛菜）いやあ でも…
But...
-In...
-In?
（愛菜）か…
（千紗･伊織）か？
It'll be an indirect kiss!
間接キスになっちゃうし
Here's my regulator.
（伊織）さっ 俺のレギュを
（愛菜）へっ!?
Are you still worried about stuff like that?
このサークルにいて
まだ そんなことが気になるのか
考えたこともなかった
I've never thought about it before.
You'll be fine. It's not an indirect kiss.
大丈夫だよ
間接キスとは違うから
そ… そうですか？
-Really?
-Remember what it's like to hold the mouthpiece?
ほら マウスピースを
くわえるときを思い出してみてよ
You're right. It's not an indirect kiss.
（愛菜）確かに
間接キスとは違いますね
（梓）そうそう
だから どっちかっていうと…
Right! It's more like...
Use my toothbrush!
（耕平）俺の歯ブラシを使いな
（伊織）あっ…
It's like sharing a toothbrush!
歯ブラシを共有してる感じだよ
That's even worse!
（愛菜）もっとイヤ！
So, what really goes on?
で 実際はどうなんだ？
We disinfect them every day.
うちでは毎日消毒してるかな
If you're still worried about it,
you could kiss directly once.
もし 気になるなら 一度
直接しちゃうのも手だけど？
Actually, I was interested in indirect kissing.
実は俺
間接キスが気になってたんです
-You're terrible.
-Despicable.
（愛菜）最低
（千紗）クズ
（愛菜）あんなの放っといて
向こうで水着 見よ
Forget about him. Let's look at swimsuits.
（千紗）確かに
水着 新調してもいいかな
You're right. Can I buy a new swimsuit?
Did I say something wrong?
俺 そんなに
ひどい発言しましたかね？
どうだろうね
Who knows.
By the way, Kotegawa...
そういえば 古手川さん
（千紗）千紗でいいよ
-You can just call me Chisa.
-Then you can call me Aina.
じゃあ 私も愛菜で
それで―
-I wanted to ask you.
-What?
ちょっと聞きたいんだけど
（千紗）何？
伊織と千紗って
つきあってるの？
Are you going out with Iori?
うう…
（愛菜）うん その顔だけで
十分 分かった
Your face gave me the answer.
Then what was that about at the Izu Spring Festival?
それなら
伊豆(いず)春祭(はるさい)のときのアレは…
ミスコンのせいでいろいろ
面倒だったから その対策に
The beauty pageant was a lot of trouble. That's why...
あ… ふうん…
-In the first place--
-Sir!
そもそも…
（店員）お客様！
（愛菜）ん？
Please change in the changing room!
（店員）着替えは
試着室でお願いします！
しまった！　いつものくせで…
Sorry, it's not our habit.
Hey, don't change in the hallway.
こらこら
通路で着替えるな 伊織
脱いだ服が邪魔になるだろう
Your clothes are in the way!
（店員）そういう問題では
ありませんが!?
That's not the problem!
-I could never imagine going out with him.
-You're right.
（千紗）あんなの相手に
そんなこと 考えられないし
（愛菜）確かに…
What happened to Kohei?
ところで 耕平はどうした？
Yeah. I haven't seen him.
そういえば 見ないな
ちょっと捜してきますよ
I'll go find him.
Oh, there he is.
おっ いたいた
（伊織）何やってんだ？　お前
-What are you doing?
-Kitahara!
北原！　お前も
ここへ導かれたのか？
So you were lead here too?
（伊織）いや
お前を捜してただけだが
No, I was just looking for you.
-You want a wetsuit?
-I wasn't planning on buying one,
（伊織）ウエットスーツが
欲しいのか？
（耕平）買う気はなかったが
これは気になっている
but I want this one!
You're right. It's a unique design.
（伊織）確かに
珍しいデザインだもんな
（耕平）ああーっ！
（伊織）なんなんだよ さっきから
What's gotten into you?
Kitahara, don't you know what anime this is from?
（耕平）北原 お前
まさか このアニメを知らない…
（伊織）これしかサイズないなら
試着は無理だな
You can't try it on in that size.
No! I don't have to be the one to wear it!
（耕平）いや これは
俺が着なくていいんだ
ん？　おお なるほど
Oh, I see.
着られるやつに頼んで
感想をもらえばいいのか
We can ask someone who fits how it feels.
（耕平）ん？
いや そういう意味じゃ…
I didn't mean--
Hey!
（伊織）おーい！
うん 着心地いいと思う
Yeah. It feels good.
ただジッパーがないタイプだから
好みが分かれるかな
It doesn't have a zipper. Some people might not like it.
Hear that, Kohei?
だとさ 耕平
う… うわあー！
I'm going to call you my best friend just for today.
俺 今日だけは
お前のこと 心の友と呼んでもいい
突然 なんだ 気色悪い
What? That's creepy.
（千紗･愛菜）ん？
Well, what are you going to do?
（伊織）で さっきのアレは
どうするんだ？
今は無理だが いずれ 必ず…
I can't buy it now, but someday...
That was a woman's wetsuit.
さっきのアレ
レディースだったんだけど？
How was it?
（寿）どうだ？　お前ら
Is there anything you want?
何か 欲しい物はあったか？
There was a lot of stuff.
いろいろあって
目移りするんですが…
I'm going to get a mask like you recommended.
とりあえず オススメどおり
マスクにしようかと
-What about you, Aina?
-I'll get a mask too.
（梓）愛菜は？
（愛菜）私もマスクにします
MASK 9,500 YEN
MASK 8,820 YEN
なあ 千紗
マスクの選び方って…
Hey, Chisa. How do I choose a mask?
ん？　千紗？
-Chisa...
-Chii-chan's so cute!
ちーちゃんってば かわいいねえ
（伊織）おわっ！
（梓）青春 青春よ！
Youth! It's youth!
（伊織）なんの話です？
What are you talking about?
（梓）いやあ 一生懸命カメラを
選んでいるのが かわいくってねえ
She's so cute looking at cameras.
Maybe she just wants to take a picture to celebrate.
記念に写真を
撮りたいってだけでは？
That's why.
だからよ
（梓）きっと 同年代で
一緒に潜れる仲間ができて―
She's probably happy that she made friends her age
she can go diving with.
うれしいんだろうね
She really loves diving, doesn't she?
あいつ よっぽど
ダイビングが好きなんですね
そうだねえ
That's right.
GRAND BLUE
（ドアが開く音）
（一同）ただいま～
We're back.
おかえりなさい… ん？
Welcome back!
-You guys bought a lot!
-Yeah.
いっぱい買ってきたのね
（伊織）はい
We bought masks.
俺たちはマスクを
（千紗）私はカメラを
I bought a camera.
（奈々華）
あらあら 頑張ったのね
Wow, you guys worked hard.
（千紗･愛菜）ん？
（伊織）頑張った？
Worked hard?
ただ 買い物をしてきた
だけですが…
We just went shopping.
ううん そうじゃなくて
That's not what I mean.
沖縄に行くお金もかかるのに
さらに機材まで買っちゃうなんて
Going to Okinawa is expensive.
And you even bought new gear!
（一同）あ…
FESTIVAL 2018
（男性たちのざわめき）
（シャッター音）
Please have a look!
ぜひ 見ていってくださーい
Have a look...
見てください…
（愛菜）うう…
（奈々華）ウフッ ウフフ…
Hey, Kitahara...
なあ 北原…
When do we go on break?
あと どれくらいで休憩なんだ
We just started a few minutes ago.
まだ 始まって
何分もたってねえよ
Hey, Kitahara.
（耕平）なあ 北原…
（伊織）黙れ 殺すぞ
Shut up. I'm going to kill you.
（シャッター音）
GRAND BLUE
（愛菜）うわあああっ！
もう お嫁に行けない！
I can't get married anymore!
You'll be fine! Yes you can!
大丈夫！　行ける行ける
What's she crying about?
俺たちなんて
ほぼ毎日 全裸だぞ
We're naked almost every day.
OKINAWA
私は向こうで
ライセンス講習を
I'll do a license class over there.
Then me and Kotobuki will go every other day.
じゃあ 俺と寿が
日替わりで そっちに
（寿）ＯＫ
Okay!
（伊織）そんなこんなで
準備を整え―
After making lots of preparations,
the time finally came for our Okinawa trip!
いよいよ 沖縄合宿へ！
（飛行機のエンジン音）
（時田）さあて お前ら―
Hey, you guys!
沖縄 到着だ！
We've arrived in Okinawa!
（一同）イエーイ！
Yeah!
Here. This is yours, Aina.
はい 愛菜ちゃんの分
No!
（耕平）ほれ 北原 マイク
Here's your mic, Kitahara.
（伊織）俺もかよ
Me too? All right, let's do this!
よっしゃ いくぜ！
-Yeah, sing your heart out.
-You guys seem to be having fun.
（寿）おお～ 歌え歌え！
（時田）ノリノリだな
♪～
A fairytale whispers
In a fake world
Hiding in the complete darkness
I reach for the forbidden fruit
In my last days
Now I know the meaning of the song about hope
A broken gear will never stop again
Even if I were to lose everything
I'd still want you to know
Trapped in the sky so far away
I'm praying with ripped off wings
Because we span together
The vows of arpeggio
If life sparkles only to the beat
Of the resonating stars
I'll sacrifice everything
Till death do us apart
Cheers!
～♪
（一同）予告をどうぞ！
Previews are coming up next!
It's so warm!
あっつーい！
It's a tropical island!
いかにも南国って感じ～
（一同）カンパーイ！
Cheers!
BUT... HOWEVER...
うわああ～！
Is this a rip current?
これは まさか離岸流！
I told you not to underestimate the sea!
（時田）だから あれほど
海はナメるなと！
THEY WERE SWEPT AWAY
BY A RIP CURRENT DURING CLASS
ON A DESERTED ISLAND
Let's go, Iori.
（時田）行くぞ 伊織
You can't cry about it forever.
（寿）いつまでも嘆いてたって
しかたないだろう
No! I can't leave his dead body here!
（伊織）イヤです！
俺は こいつのなきがらを―
ここに放置していくなんて
できません！
He's my best friend!
親友なんですよ…
My first, and last...
俺の 最初で最後の…
THE DEATH OF A FRIEND.
IT HAS NO MEANING.
AND A MAN-EATING SHARK APPEARS.
（時田）あの人食いザメを
どうするか…
What should we do about that man-eating shark?
（寿）あれはやっかいだな
What a pain.
Why don't we lure it in with Kohei's corpse?
（伊織）耕平の死体を餌にして
おびき出したら どうすかね？
CAN IORI AND THE OTHERS SURVIVE!?
Grand Blue Dreaming
DEPENDING ON CIRCUMSTANCES, THE
PRESENTATION, ACTING, AND CONTENT MAY DIFFER.
こっちの部屋なら
手足も伸ばせるでしょ？
We can stretch out in this room.
We have to rest well for the class.
ライセンス講習のためにも
きちんと寝ないとね
Goodnight!
じゃあ おやすみ
おやすみなさい
NEXT EPISODE
"ARRIVAL IN OKINAWA"
（伊織）ハッ！